[{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f950219","correctAnswer":"Michael Fish ","incorrectAnswers":["Gordon Jones","Harry Mortimer","Brian Daniels"],"question":"Which BBC Weather Man Famously Denied Reports Of A Possible Hurricane In 1987?","tags":["general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc94","correctAnswer":"Blatherskite","incorrectAnswers":["Agastopia","Cacophony","Impignorate"],"question":"Which word is defined as 'a person who talks at great length without making much sense'?","tags":["words","general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"6239f843a72e7a347ac879da","correctAnswer":"Yankee","incorrectAnswers":["Yearly","Yum","Yurt"],"question":"What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter Y?","tags":["words","language","general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"easy","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f950323","correctAnswer":"Charles Manson","incorrectAnswers":["Ed Gein","Ted Bundy","Jim Jones"],"question":"Who was the man convicted of masterminding the 1969 LaBianca-Tate murders?","tags":["general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c3a","correctAnswer":"Testicles","incorrectAnswers":["Eyes","Fists","Arms"],"question":"'Christmas Crackers' is cockney rhyming slang for which body part?","tags":["general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f950121","correctAnswer":"Gold","incorrectAnswers":["Invisible","Dead","Water"],"question":"What does the \"touch of Midas\" turn everything?","tags":["mythology","general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"easy","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"622a1c377cc59eab6f950423","correctAnswer":"Oracle","incorrectAnswers":["Microsoft","Yahoo","Google"],"question":"In the year 2000 which companies CEO was the worlds second richest man?","tags":["general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc5c","correctAnswer":"Sprunt","incorrectAnswers":["Bumfuzzle","Salopettes","Kakorrhaphiophobia"],"question":"Which word is defined as 'an old Scottish word meaning to chase girls around among the haystacks after dark'?","tags":["words","general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc73","correctAnswer":"Impignorate","incorrectAnswers":["Dipthong","Deipnophobia","Erf"],"question":"Which word is defined as 'to pawn or mortgage something'?","tags":["words","general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"General Knowledge","id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f9503b9","correctAnswer":"New Mexico","incorrectAnswers":["Nagasaki","Hiroshima","Bikini Atoll"],"question":"Where did the first atomic bomb explode?","tags":["wars","general_knowledge"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false}]